{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817725816","data":{"timestamp":" 946817725815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817726453","data":{"timestamp":" 946817726452"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817726709","data":{"timestamp":" 946817726708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817727278","data":{"timestamp":" 946817727277"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817728435","data":{"timestamp":" 946817728434"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817729208","data":{"timestamp":" 946817729207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SANA"," userResponse":" SANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817730613","data":{"timestamp":" 946817730612"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817731121","data":{"timestamp":" 946817731120"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817731214","data":{"timestamp":" 946817731214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 6ef9926c-5699-4375-9b1f-588d4bd7cb3a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIISHI"," userResponse":" ALIISHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817759643","data":{"timestamp":" 946817759643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hadi_mawe-tatu-hadi"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hadi"," userResponse":" hadi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817768501","data":{"timestamp":" 946817768501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hapa_hapa-lala-kipi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hapa"," userResponse":" hapa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817778067","data":{"timestamp":" 946817778067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_nini-hana-baba"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817786588","data":{"timestamp":" 946817786588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hana_hana-wetu-boga"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hana"," userResponse":" hana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817796557","data":{"timestamp":" 946817796557"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hadi_hadi-pana-wapi"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hadi"," userResponse":" hadi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817806286","data":{"timestamp":" 946817806286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_mume-haha-tuwe"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817815248","data":{"timestamp":" 946817815248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haki_yeye-haki-mara"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haki"," userResponse":" haki"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817824372","data":{"timestamp":" 946817824372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_haha_pole-haha-babu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" haha"," userResponse":" haha"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817833384","data":{"timestamp":" 946817833383"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hayo_papo-hayo-kazi"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hayo"," userResponse":" hayo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817843625","data":{"timestamp":" 946817843625"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_hadi_koko-hadi-pesa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" hadi"," userResponse":" hadi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817849395","data":{"timestamp":" 946817849395"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 0a717b5f-960f-4927-be30-97c74158c937"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ha.noShow.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_hadi_koko-hadi-pesa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817883249","data":{"timestamp":" 946817883248"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817886359","data":{"timestamp":" 946817886358"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817887964","data":{"timestamp":" 946817887963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817890843","data":{"timestamp":" 946817890842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817892473","data":{"timestamp":" 946817892472"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817895288","data":{"timestamp":" 946817895287"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817896887","data":{"timestamp":" 946817896886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817899656","data":{"timestamp":" 946817899655"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hadi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HADI"," userResponse":" HADI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817901263","data":{"timestamp":" 946817901262"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817904059","data":{"timestamp":" 946817904058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817905672","data":{"timestamp":" 946817905671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817908315","data":{"timestamp":" 946817908314"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817909912","data":{"timestamp":" 946817909911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKI"," userResponse":" HAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817912484","data":{"timestamp":" 946817912484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAKI"," userResponse":" HAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817914088","data":{"timestamp":" 946817914088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817917082","data":{"timestamp":" 946817917081"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817918696","data":{"timestamp":" 946817918695"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAHA"," userResponse":" HAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817921824","data":{"timestamp":" 946817921823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAHA"," userResponse":" HAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817923443","data":{"timestamp":" 946817923442"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817926128","data":{"timestamp":" 946817926127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::begin.wrd.ha.rand.18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817928152","data":{"timestamp":" 946817928150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" hapo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817928249","data":{"timestamp":" 946817928249"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 85963119-307c-4b48-9c90-d6ab50a5664a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__begin.wrd.ha.rand.18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817944412","data":{"timestamp":" 946817944411"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817945479","data":{"timestamp":" 946817945479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haya"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817949228","data":{"timestamp":" 946817949227"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817950285","data":{"timestamp":" 946817950284"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HASA"," userResponse":" HASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817954730","data":{"timestamp":" 946817954729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817955786","data":{"timestamp":" 946817955785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HALI"," userResponse":" HALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817960386","data":{"timestamp":" 946817960385"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817961448","data":{"timestamp":" 946817961447"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hata"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HATA"," userResponse":" HATA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817966258","data":{"timestamp":" 946817966258"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817967338","data":{"timestamp":" 946817967338"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hamu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAMU"," userResponse":" HAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817972005","data":{"timestamp":" 946817972005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817973044","data":{"timestamp":" 946817973043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hayo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817977576","data":{"timestamp":" 946817977575"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817978635","data":{"timestamp":" 946817978635"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hana"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HANA"," userResponse":" HANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817982646","data":{"timestamp":" 946817982646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAHA"," userResponse":" HAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817983715","data":{"timestamp":" 946817983714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" haha"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAHA"," userResponse":" HAHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817991319","data":{"timestamp":" 946817991318"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817992380","data":{"timestamp":" 946817992379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hapa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPA"," userResponse":" HAPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817996722","data":{"timestamp":" 946817996721"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946817997778","data":{"timestamp":" 946817997778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::begin.wrd.ha.rand.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818001235","data":{"timestamp":" 946818001233"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" hawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818001367","data":{"timestamp":" 946818001367"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 4eae9b51-4bcb-4210-863f-63181d7c5cb1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__begin.wrd.ha.rand.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" hawa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAWA"," userResponse":" HAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818034696","data":{"timestamp":" 946818034696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818037555","data":{"timestamp":" 946818037554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818046901","data":{"timestamp":" 946818046901"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818049586","data":{"timestamp":" 946818049586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818059621","data":{"timestamp":" 946818059621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818062316","data":{"timestamp":" 946818062316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818072913","data":{"timestamp":" 946818072913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818075111","data":{"timestamp":" 946818075111"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818082276","data":{"timestamp":" 946818082276"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818094574","data":{"timestamp":" 946818094574"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818097582","data":{"timestamp":" 946818097582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818107973","data":{"timestamp":" 946818107973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818110886","data":{"timestamp":" 946818110886"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818121749","data":{"timestamp":" 946818121748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818124312","data":{"timestamp":" 946818124312"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818134209","data":{"timestamp":" 946818134209"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818136432","data":{"timestamp":" 946818136432"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818146691","data":{"timestamp":" 946818146690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818149584","data":{"timestamp":" 946818149584"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818159514","data":{"timestamp":" 946818159514"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818174374","data":{"timestamp":" 946818174374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_WRONG - FTR_ERROR_CHAR"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818183716","data":{"timestamp":" 946818183716"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818186696","data":{"timestamp":" 946818186696"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" _"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" FTR_RIGHT"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.missingLtr:lc.begin.ha.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818201819","data":{"timestamp":" 946818201816"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f8142027-ab4e-46ac-acf8-5b803ec4e83d"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.missingLtr_lc.begin.ha.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_ha__"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818214332","data":{"timestamp":" 946818214331"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALI"," userResponse":" KALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818217280","data":{"timestamp":" 946818217279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kaka"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAKA"," userResponse":" KAKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818220337","data":{"timestamp":" 946818220336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kazi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAZI"," userResponse":" KAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818223498","data":{"timestamp":" 946818223497"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kale"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818226596","data":{"timestamp":" 946818226596"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kapu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAPU"," userResponse":" KAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818229629","data":{"timestamp":" 946818229628"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kavu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAVU"," userResponse":" KAVU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818232555","data":{"timestamp":" 946818232555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KAMA"," userResponse":" KAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818235595","data":{"timestamp":" 946818235594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASI"," userResponse":" KASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818238654","data":{"timestamp":" 946818238653"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" karo"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KARO"," userResponse":" KARO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818241660","data":{"timestamp":" 946818241659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::begin.wrd.ka.rand.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818245351","data":{"timestamp":" 946818245349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818245478","data":{"timestamp":" 946818245477"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 56bf8532-ef64-468f-9f55-06ea17bca5f2"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__begin.wrd.ka.rand.2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" kasa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KASA"," userResponse":" KASA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818263966","data":{"timestamp":" 946818263966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kapu_simu-kapu-kisa"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kapu"," userResponse":" kapu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818273377","data":{"timestamp":" 946818273377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kasi_nane-ziwa-kasi"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kasi"," userResponse":" kasi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818283274","data":{"timestamp":" 946818283274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kale_kiti-wiki-kale"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kale"," userResponse":" kale"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818292525","data":{"timestamp":" 946818292525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kati_yaya-ebei-kati"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kati"," userResponse":" kati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818301675","data":{"timestamp":" 946818301675"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_kama-mzee-nane"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kama"," userResponse":" kama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818312015","data":{"timestamp":" 946818312015"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kapu_kapu-mmea-hema"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kapu"," userResponse":" kapu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818321506","data":{"timestamp":" 946818321506"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_ndio-elsa-kama"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kama"," userResponse":" kama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818331046","data":{"timestamp":" 946818331046"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kavu_haha-zamu-kavu"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kavu"," userResponse":" kavu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818340349","data":{"timestamp":" 946818340349"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_kali-lulu-kiio"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818351056","data":{"timestamp":" 946818351056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_tele-zipu-kama"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kama"," userResponse":" kama"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.show.3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818356840","data":{"timestamp":" 946818356839"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 2656f9ea-56b9-4275-a266-17f9f6d4e93b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.show.3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kama_tele-zipu-kama"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818373566","data":{"timestamp":" 946818373566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818374080","data":{"timestamp":" 946818374080"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818374785","data":{"timestamp":" 946818374785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818375951","data":{"timestamp":" 946818375950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" ANALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818383265","data":{"timestamp":" 946818383265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818385058","data":{"timestamp":" 946818385058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818396736","data":{"timestamp":" 946818396735"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818402363","data":{"timestamp":" 946818402363"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818405036","data":{"timestamp":" 946818405036"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818406023","data":{"timestamp":" 946818406022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818406599","data":{"timestamp":" 946818406598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818409053","data":{"timestamp":" 946818409053"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818410461","data":{"timestamp":" 946818410461"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" START_ANAHISI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818412299","data":{"timestamp":" 946818412298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818414003","data":{"timestamp":" 946818414003"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818415899","data":{"timestamp":" 946818415898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818416432","data":{"timestamp":" 946818416431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818417217","data":{"timestamp":" 946818417216"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818418591","data":{"timestamp":" 946818418591"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818420655","data":{"timestamp":" 946818420654"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818420950","data":{"timestamp":" 946818420950"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818421744","data":{"timestamp":" 946818421743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818423378","data":{"timestamp":" 946818423377"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" START_AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818424239","data":{"timestamp":" 946818424238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818426185","data":{"timestamp":" 946818426184"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818428084","data":{"timestamp":" 946818428084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818428244","data":{"timestamp":" 946818428243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818428546","data":{"timestamp":" 946818428545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818429057","data":{"timestamp":" 946818429056"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818433028","data":{"timestamp":" 946818433028"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818433198","data":{"timestamp":" 946818433198"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818434207","data":{"timestamp":" 946818434206"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" START_MSICHANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818435384","data":{"timestamp":" 946818435384"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" START_AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818437316","data":{"timestamp":" 946818437315"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818438802","data":{"timestamp":" 946818438802"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818443195","data":{"timestamp":" 946818443195"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818445092","data":{"timestamp":" 946818445091"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818445849","data":{"timestamp":" 946818445848"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818446403","data":{"timestamp":" 946818446403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818447222","data":{"timestamp":" 946818447221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818448185","data":{"timestamp":" 946818448185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818450098","data":{"timestamp":" 946818450098"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818450804","data":{"timestamp":" 946818450803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818452288","data":{"timestamp":" 946818452288"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818452799","data":{"timestamp":" 946818452799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818454405","data":{"timestamp":" 946818454404"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818456334","data":{"timestamp":" 946818456333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818456829","data":{"timestamp":" 946818456828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818457476","data":{"timestamp":" 946818457475"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818458948","data":{"timestamp":" 946818458947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" ANACHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818460692","data":{"timestamp":" 946818460692"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818460857","data":{"timestamp":" 946818460857"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818461589","data":{"timestamp":" 946818461588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818462193","data":{"timestamp":" 946818462192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" START_ANACHEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818463038","data":{"timestamp":" 946818463038"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818464738","data":{"timestamp":" 946818464737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818466729","data":{"timestamp":" 946818466728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818467455","data":{"timestamp":" 946818467454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818468742","data":{"timestamp":" 946818468741"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" AMESOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818470054","data":{"timestamp":" 946818470054"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" KICHEKESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818472048","data":{"timestamp":" 946818472047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818472235","data":{"timestamp":" 946818472234"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" START_SABABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818473354","data":{"timestamp":" 946818473354"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" START_AMESOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818475108","data":{"timestamp":" 946818475107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818476694","data":{"timestamp":" 946818476694"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" AMESOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818477167","data":{"timestamp":" 946818477167"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" AMESOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818478596","data":{"timestamp":" 946818478595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" START_KICHEKESHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818480416","data":{"timestamp":" 946818480416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818483155","data":{"timestamp":" 946818483155"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818483345","data":{"timestamp":" 946818483345"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818483680","data":{"timestamp":" 946818483680"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" WANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818484492","data":{"timestamp":" 946818484491"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818484521","data":{"timestamp":" 946818484521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818488941","data":{"timestamp":" 946818488940"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" START_WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818490148","data":{"timestamp":" 946818490148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818491810","data":{"timestamp":" 946818491809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818493007","data":{"timestamp":" 946818493006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818494638","data":{"timestamp":" 946818494637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818496051","data":{"timestamp":" 946818496050"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" START_WANASOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818498599","data":{"timestamp":" 946818498598"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" WANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818500286","data":{"timestamp":" 946818500286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818501945","data":{"timestamp":" 946818501944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818504323","data":{"timestamp":" 946818504322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818505052","data":{"timestamp":" 946818505051"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818506266","data":{"timestamp":" 946818506266"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818507401","data":{"timestamp":" 946818507401"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818508968","data":{"timestamp":" 946818508968"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818509567","data":{"timestamp":" 946818509567"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818510781","data":{"timestamp":" 946818510781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818511376","data":{"timestamp":" 946818511376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818514180","data":{"timestamp":" 946818514179"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818515287","data":{"timestamp":" 946818515286"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONA"," userResponse":" ANAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818515953","data":{"timestamp":" 946818515952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818518352","data":{"timestamp":" 946818518351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818518925","data":{"timestamp":" 946818518925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONA"," userResponse":" ANAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818519940","data":{"timestamp":" 946818519939"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818521962","data":{"timestamp":" 946818521960"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818522093","data":{"timestamp":" 946818522093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 51dfd29e-4f04-421b-acf6-f9ff28d9d6ea"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818538109","data":{"timestamp":" 946818538109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818538431","data":{"timestamp":" 946818538430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818539214","data":{"timestamp":" 946818539214"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818540023","data":{"timestamp":" 946818540022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818541965","data":{"timestamp":" 946818541965"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818543646","data":{"timestamp":" 946818543646"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818545059","data":{"timestamp":" 946818545058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818545573","data":{"timestamp":" 946818545572"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818546280","data":{"timestamp":" 946818546279"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTOTO"," userResponse":" MTOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818547446","data":{"timestamp":" 946818547445"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mtoto analia?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANALIA"," userResponse":" ANALIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818551089","data":{"timestamp":" 946818551088"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818552168","data":{"timestamp":" 946818552168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818552697","data":{"timestamp":" 946818552697"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" START_NJAA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818554465","data":{"timestamp":" 946818554464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818556587","data":{"timestamp":" 946818556586"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818557574","data":{"timestamp":" 946818557573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818558152","data":{"timestamp":" 946818558150"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anahisi njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818561372","data":{"timestamp":" 946818561372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818561665","data":{"timestamp":" 946818561665"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818562373","data":{"timestamp":" 946818562373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818563878","data":{"timestamp":" 946818563877"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" START_AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818564843","data":{"timestamp":" 946818564842"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" START_AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818566803","data":{"timestamp":" 946818566803"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818568166","data":{"timestamp":" 946818568165"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818568700","data":{"timestamp":" 946818568700"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818569490","data":{"timestamp":" 946818569489"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MVULANA"," userResponse":" MVULANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818570875","data":{"timestamp":" 946818570875"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mvulana amehuzunika?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," userResponse":" AMEHUZUNIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818575693","data":{"timestamp":" 946818575693"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818577805","data":{"timestamp":" 946818577805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818579371","data":{"timestamp":" 946818579371"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" START_ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818581299","data":{"timestamp":" 946818581298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818582221","data":{"timestamp":" 946818582220"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818584329","data":{"timestamp":" 946818584328"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818585777","data":{"timestamp":" 946818585776"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818587739","data":{"timestamp":" 946818587739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818588950","data":{"timestamp":" 946818588949"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAMKOSA"," userResponse":" ANAMKOSA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818589465","data":{"timestamp":" 946818589464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818590149","data":{"timestamp":" 946818590148"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anamkosa baba yake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAKE"," userResponse":" YAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818595451","data":{"timestamp":" 946818595450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818595720","data":{"timestamp":" 946818595719"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818596595","data":{"timestamp":" 946818596595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818598462","data":{"timestamp":" 946818598462"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" START_MSICHANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818600343","data":{"timestamp":" 946818600342"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818602403","data":{"timestamp":" 946818602403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" START_AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818604738","data":{"timestamp":" 946818604738"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818606130","data":{"timestamp":" 946818606128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818606593","data":{"timestamp":" 946818606593"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818607409","data":{"timestamp":" 946818607408"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSICHANA"," userResponse":" MSICHANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818609143","data":{"timestamp":" 946818609142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini msichana amefurahi?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMEFURAHI"," userResponse":" AMEFURAHI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818612204","data":{"timestamp":" 946818612204"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818612484","data":{"timestamp":" 946818612484"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" START_SABABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818613690","data":{"timestamp":" 946818613689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818615483","data":{"timestamp":" 946818615483"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818616853","data":{"timestamp":" 946818616853"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818616968","data":{"timestamp":" 946818616967"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818618441","data":{"timestamp":" 946818618440"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818619974","data":{"timestamp":" 946818619973"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" START_JIPYA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818621910","data":{"timestamp":" 946818621910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818623308","data":{"timestamp":" 946818623308"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818624066","data":{"timestamp":" 946818624066"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818624620","data":{"timestamp":" 946818624619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANA"," userResponse":" ANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818625437","data":{"timestamp":" 946818625436"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RINDA"," userResponse":" RINDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818626404","data":{"timestamp":" 946818626403"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu ana rinda jipya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JIPYA"," userResponse":" JIPYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818630759","data":{"timestamp":" 946818630759"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818630972","data":{"timestamp":" 946818630972"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818631951","data":{"timestamp":" 946818631951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818632606","data":{"timestamp":" 946818632606"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" START_ANACHEKA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818633446","data":{"timestamp":" 946818633446"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818635124","data":{"timestamp":" 946818635123"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818636501","data":{"timestamp":" 946818636500"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818636996","data":{"timestamp":" 946818636996"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818637642","data":{"timestamp":" 946818637641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MZEE"," userResponse":" MZEE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818639117","data":{"timestamp":" 946818639117"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mzee anacheka?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANACHEKA"," userResponse":" ANACHEKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818642800","data":{"timestamp":" 946818642799"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818643123","data":{"timestamp":" 946818643122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" START_SABABU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818645673","data":{"timestamp":" 946818645673"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818647071","data":{"timestamp":" 946818647071"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" START_AMESOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818649515","data":{"timestamp":" 946818649515"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" AMESOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818651006","data":{"timestamp":" 946818651006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" START_KICHEKESHO"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818653626","data":{"timestamp":" 946818653626"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" KICHEKESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818655068","data":{"timestamp":" 946818655068"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818655795","data":{"timestamp":" 946818655794"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABABU"," userResponse":" SABABU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818657084","data":{"timestamp":" 946818657083"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AMESOMA"," userResponse":" AMESOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818658400","data":{"timestamp":" 946818658399"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa sababu amesoma kichekesho."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHEKESHO"," userResponse":" KICHEKESHO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818664428","data":{"timestamp":" 946818664428"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818664600","data":{"timestamp":" 946818664600"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818666032","data":{"timestamp":" 946818666032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818667337","data":{"timestamp":" 946818667336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818668952","data":{"timestamp":" 946818668952"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_ANATABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818669778","data":{"timestamp":" 946818669778"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" START_ANATABASAMU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818671672","data":{"timestamp":" 946818671671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818673070","data":{"timestamp":" 946818673070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818673564","data":{"timestamp":" 946818673563"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818674074","data":{"timestamp":" 946818674074"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818674583","data":{"timestamp":" 946818674582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818676421","data":{"timestamp":" 946818676421"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa nini mama huyu anatabasamu?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANATABASAMU"," userResponse":" ANATABASAMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818680293","data":{"timestamp":" 946818680293"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818681000","data":{"timestamp":" 946818680999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818682614","data":{"timestamp":" 946818682614"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" START_WANASOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818684517","data":{"timestamp":" 946818684517"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 2"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" START_WANASOMA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818686232","data":{"timestamp":" 946818686232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" AUTO_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818687824","data":{"timestamp":" 946818687824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818688324","data":{"timestamp":" 946818688324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818690517","data":{"timestamp":" 946818690516"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818691041","data":{"timestamp":" 946818691040"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818692183","data":{"timestamp":" 946818692182"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANASOMA"," userResponse":" WANASOMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818693006","data":{"timestamp":" 946818693005"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818693972","data":{"timestamp":" 946818693971"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto wake wanasoma kimya kimya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIMYA"," userResponse":" KIMYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818698563","data":{"timestamp":" 946818698562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818699271","data":{"timestamp":" 946818699271"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818700945","data":{"timestamp":" 946818700945"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818702268","data":{"timestamp":" 946818702268"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818704070","data":{"timestamp":" 946818704069"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818704792","data":{"timestamp":" 946818704791"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYU"," userResponse":" HUYU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818706007","data":{"timestamp":" 946818706006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAHISI"," userResponse":" ANAHISI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818707143","data":{"timestamp":" 946818707142"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama huyu anahisi nini?"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINI"," userResponse":" NINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818710913","data":{"timestamp":" 946818710913"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818711621","data":{"timestamp":" 946818711620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONA"," userResponse":" ANAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818712814","data":{"timestamp":" 946818712814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818715068","data":{"timestamp":" 946818715067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NADHANI"," userResponse":" NADHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818716175","data":{"timestamp":" 946818716174"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANAONA"," userResponse":" ANAONA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818716840","data":{"timestamp":" 946818716840"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818719590","data":{"timestamp":" 946818719588"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818719750","data":{"timestamp":" 946818719749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" 81a21d71-cdb8-4f3b-a2af-9d7002259c50"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Nadhani anaona haya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYA"," userResponse":" HAYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818749379","data":{"timestamp":" 946818749378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kasa_giza-kasa-mvua"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kasa"," userResponse":" kasa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818757894","data":{"timestamp":" 946818757893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kata_kata-kosa-saba"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kata"," userResponse":" kata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818767285","data":{"timestamp":" 946818767285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_bila-bali-kali"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818776566","data":{"timestamp":" 946818776565"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kali_zizi-miti-kali"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kali"," userResponse":" kali"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818785771","data":{"timestamp":" 946818785771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kati_kati-saba-kosa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kati"," userResponse":" kati"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818794814","data":{"timestamp":" 946818794814"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kata_huku-choo-kata"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kata"," userResponse":" kata"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818804820","data":{"timestamp":" 946818804820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_tena-kiwe-kato"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kato"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818814518","data":{"timestamp":" 946818814518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kana_nini-nayo-kana"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kana"," userResponse":" kana"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818824490","data":{"timestamp":" 946818824490"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_ziwe-kato-nami"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kato"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818833502","data":{"timestamp":" 946818833501"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_nawe-kule-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kule"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818842618","data":{"timestamp":" 946818842618"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_nawe-kule-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kule"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818852898","data":{"timestamp":" 946818852898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_nawe-kule-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kato"," userResponse":" kato"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946818858678","data":{"timestamp":" 946818858677"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000102_155454"," gameId":" f81750bf-779d-4eb8-b0ab-d984f559c903"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_begin.wrd.ka.noShow.4"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_kato_nawe-kule-kato"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}